The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Coast
Allheaven Star System
No way...
We're really back !
I didn't die in that godforsaken place !
Master really did it !
He broke the Thunder Celestial Temple's formation single-handedly
and saved us all.
Senior Xu Mu,
I will remember your great kindness !
From now on,
Master's name
will be praised throughout Allheaven.
Did you hear ?
Xu Mu, all alone,
killed 3 Thunder Celestial Messengers !
Really ?
Old man, hurry up and tell us !
The Thunder Celestial Realm collapsed, and then what ?
Right, what exactly happened to Xu Mu ?
Tell us now.
You're killing us with suspense, just tell us !
That day, all the cultivators closed their eyes
and faced their death.
Storming the Thunder Celestial Temple's teleportation formation
is a crime worthy of having their families exterminated.
But Xu Mu showed no fear at all.
He fought the 3 messengers until blood poured from their orifices
and their Origin Souls scattered !
Ancestral Hall
Zhan Family
Lie Yunzi
Zhan Family Head
Is it true ?
Absolutely true.
But the teleportation formation was shattered
and everyone was randomly sent across Allheaven.
Senior Xu Mu
hasn't been found yet.
This child is courageous and scheming
but he's also a bit too high-profile.
He will surely attract countless enemies.
Our Zhan Family must not get too close to him.
But we mustn't
become his enemy either.
I wonder where exactly Senior is.
Strange Domain
Western Domain
Allheaven Star System
What is this place ?
The fog fears light.
It's almost like a living creature.
My Divine Sense is blocked too ?
Spatial Bending !
This path is blocked.
3 days later
Everything within 10 000 li of this thing is sealed.
Does this place really have no exit ?
Could it be...
Reed Marsh
Chosen Immortal Clan
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) Celestials from above,
Ah Qing
Chosen Immortal Clan member
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) please protect our clan
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) from the demons.
A shapeshifting fog beast !
This tattoo...
The Forsaken Immortal Clan ?
Clan Head !
Clan Head
Forsaken Immortal Clan
Activate the formation
to strangle the fog beast !
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) Here comes evil and filth,
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) we beseech your divine might.
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) Celestial Slaughter Formation,
(Chosen Immortal Clan's language) activate !
This...
This is...
That's right,
this is it.
This is it !
Clan Head !
What are you doing ?
This lowly one
pays respects to Upper Celestial.
Upper Celestial ?
Our Chosen Immortal Clan
has followed Master Celestial's decree for generations
and guarded the Mysterious Yin Cauldron
for 30 000 years.
You've finally arrived !
Why aren't you kneeling !?
Chosen Immortal Clan ?
Forsaken Immortal Clan ?
Their name is almost the same.
Upper Celestial possesses the Withered Dao Pair,
so you must be someone close to Celestial King Carefree.
This lowly one was foolish.
I failed to recognize the Celestial Envoy's identity earlier,
this is truly a capital offense.
Withered Dao Pair ?
So it was his artifact.
Judging by their reaction,
they must not know that the Celestial Realm has collapsed.
He really is an Celestial Envoy ?
Aren't Celestials just legends ?
When was the last time Celestial King Carefree
last came ?
The Celestial King issued his final celestial decree
and he never returned
during tens of thousands of years.
To be honest with Upper Celestial,
you are the first Celestial I have seen in my life.
They really don't know the Celestial Realm has collapsed...
Celestial Envoy's visit must be
to retrieve the Mysterious Yin Cauldron
for the Celestial King.
Mysterious Yin Cauldron ?
Where is
that cauldron ?
Upper Celestial,
please follow me.
Residential area
Chosen Immortal Clan
Be careful.
Slow down, slow down.
Mom...
Mom !
It's not a fog beast,
it's a Celestial !
The child is young
and ignorant.
Upper Celestial, please forgive her.
Our clan has never had visitors.
What are those fog beasts
you spoke of ?
This place has a naturally formed fog.
And the fog has a spirit.
It condenses into physical form
and becomes a fog beast.
Fog beasts are bloodthirsty by nature.
Once they appear,
they kill everyone they see
until they die.
This formation was personally laid by Celestial King Carefree.
With this formation,
we were able to protect ourselves.
It is indeed the work of a Celestial
but we can't hold out much longer.
Each year,
the fog beasts grow more numerous.
Some can even take human forms.
To this day,
we have suffered countless casualties.
Upper Celestial,
the Mysterious Yin Cauldron is just ahead.
Please follow me.
Clan Head !
You can't take this person to the Mysterious Yin Cauldron !
It's Ta Shan !
Ta Shan
Chosen Immortal Clan member
He's being disrespectful to the Celestial ?
Demon,
get away from the Clan Head !
Ta Shan,
this is an Upper Celestial.
Don't be insolent !
Upper Celestial ?
Clan Head,
those are stories we tell children.
After all this time,
you've started believing them yourself !?
Ta Shan !
13 leaves ?
Equivalent of Corporeal Yang.
Ta Shan !
He broke my Imprisoning Fist with a single step ?
Again !
He opened all his tattoos !
Back on Planet Suzaku, the Warriors
already had formidable physiques.
With 13 leaves,
it's really extraordinary.
Tattoos transforming into armor ?
When it comes to battle incantations,
he's reached the pinnacle of body enhancement.
What a pity...
You're too weak
to fight me.
Stop !
A celestial spell !
Could it be...
that he really is a Celestial ?
Upper Celestial, calm your anger.
I beg Upper Celestial to spare Ta Shan's life.
Ta Shan has cultivated bitterly since childhood
and cares about his responsibilities to the altar
and the celestial decree.
Since the fog beasts appeared,
many of our clansmen died.
Only Ta Shan dares to risk his life to protect us.
The way he offended you
was not a form of disrespect.
Grandpa,
say no more.
Even if he really is a Celestial,
why did he wait until today ?
Why did he appear at this very moment !?
The celestial decree...
Generation after generation, we've obeyed that decree that might not even exist !
And did we get in return !?
All of this
is simply not worth it !
Celestial Spirit Armor !
Ta Shan,
do you have a death wish ?
A Scattered Demon Armor ?
This demonic energy isn't dense,
it seems suppressed by some other power.
Today,
even if you really are a Celestial,
I, Ta Shan,
will kill you !
If a Celestial wants to kill you,
then you will kill the Celestial ?
Interesting...
What is this !?
Such a huge thing !
You will...
break for me !
Fall !
Ta Shan !
Ta Shan...
I'm...
still alive ?
If I wanted to kill you,
the first strike
would've been enough.
Thank you for sparing him, Upper Celestial !
The fog is rising ?
The fog beasts are coming !
It's the fog beasts !
Damn it...
Now of all times...
Quickly activate the Celestial King's formation !
It can be purified within half an incense stick of time.
Everyone stay on guard,
don't let the human-shaped fog beasts appear.
Thankfully it's just a false alarm.
Something's wrong.
Clan Head !
Why are there so many ?
The formation is broken !
How is this possible ?
Fight them !
Buy me some time,
I'll reactivate the celestial formation !
Follow me !
Don't let them in !
How many are there ?
Dao of the Underworld,
Underworld River !
Upper Celestial, you mustn't !
That's...
A human-shaped fog beast !
Any spell that can't kill it in single strike
will be ineffective the second time.
It can even copy your spells.
Good...
Delicious...
It's adapting to my sword techniques ?
Your speed can't match it !
Is that so ?
Stop !
Withered Dao Pair,
go !
Scatter.
The fog beasts are gone !
They're all dead ?
They're all dead !
This is the might of a true Celestial.
Thank you, Upper Celestial,
for saving our Chosen Immortal Clan.
Thank you, Upper Celestial !
Is this
what a Celestial is ?
Celestial King Carefree ordered the Chosen Immortal Clan to guard this place.
And the fog beasts are also naturally born in this place.
Mysterious Yin Cauldron...
Fog beasts...
Celestials...
What's the link
between them ?
Now,
take me to the Mysterious Yin Cauldron.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
by a child's steadfast heart ?
Nascent Soul
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
stand in the way,
Soul Transformation
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
Ascendant
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.